{
    "Questions": [
        {
          "question":       "Who is the first Nepali to win the victoria cross award?",
          "optionOne":      "Kumar Thapa",
          "optionTwo":      "Damar Bahadur Thapa",
          "optionThree":    "Kul Thapa",
          "optionFour":     "Kulbir Thapa",
          "rightAnswer":    "optionFour",
          "audiencePoll":   "5, 10, 5, 80, 0",
          "amount":         "5,000",
          "information":    "Kulbir Thapa was the first nepali to win the Victoria Cross award!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Who won the noble prize in medicine in 2022?",
            "optionOne":   "Michael Houghton",
            "optionTwo":   "Sir Peter J. Ratcliffe",
            "optionThree": "Tasuku Honjo",
            "optionFour":  "Svante Pääbo",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "Who is known as the tiger of the house in Nepal?",
            "optionOne":   "Bhimsen Thapa",
            "optionTwo":   "Chandra Sumsher",
            "optionThree": "Balbhadra Kunwar",
            "optionFour":  "Kalu Pandey",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "When is world music day celebrated?",
            "optionOne":   "Jun 21",
            "optionTwo":   "July 21",
            "optionThree": "September 19",
            "optionFour":  "November 19",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "In which province of China is Wuhan located?",
            "optionOne":   "Shanghai",
            "optionTwo":   "Shenzhen",
            "optionThree": "Hubei",
            "optionFour":  "Hebai",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "Which is the deepest canyon in the world",
            "optionOne":   "Yarlung Zangbo Grand Canyon",
            "optionTwo":   "Colca Canyon",
            "optionThree": "Namucuo Canyon",
            "optionFour":  "Makhaleng River Canyon",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "After the Moon, what is the brightest object in the night sky?",
            "optionOne":   "Betelgeuse",
            "optionTwo":   "Pole star",
            "optionThree": "Venus",
            "optionFour":  "International Space Station",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "In which year, did the trolly bus service commence in Nepal?",
            "optionOne":   "2032 B.S",
            "optionTwo":   "2025 B.S",
            "optionThree": "2031 B.S",
            "optionFour":  "2022 B.S",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "Which country has won the most number of gold medals in the Olympics?",
            "optionOne":   "China",
            "optionTwo":   "U.S.A",
            "optionThree": "Germany",
            "optionFour":  "Japan",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "Which is the fastest commerical aeroplane of the world?",
            "optionOne":   "Boeing 747-8 Intercontinental",
            "optionTwo":   "Airbus A350",
            "optionThree": "Boeing 787-10 Dreamliner",
            "optionFour":  "Concorde",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },
         {
            "question":    "Which is the best selling video game of all time?",
            "optionOne":   "Tetris",
            "optionTwo":   "Minecraft",
            "optionThree": "GTA V",
            "optionFour":  "Wii Sport",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "Which is the largest car manufacturing company",
            "optionOne":   "Ford",
            "optionTwo":   "Tesla",
            "optionThree": "Toyota",
            "optionFour":  "Volkswagen",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "In which year did A Levels commence in Nepal?",
            "optionOne":   "1986 A.D",
            "optionTwo":   "1997 A.D",
            "optionThree": "2002 A.D",
            "optionFour":  "2001 A.D",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "Which University offered the first-ever academic programme in Computer Science?",
            "optionOne":   "Harvard University",
            "optionTwo":   "University of Glasgow",
            "optionThree": "Cambridge University",
            "optionFour":  "MIT",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        },{
            "question":    "Who was the royal priest of Prithivi Narayan Shah?",
            "optionOne":   "Gaureshwor Pant",
            "optionTwo":   "Kulananda Dhakal",
            "optionThree": "Vrajanath Poudyal",
            "optionFour":  "Durga Prasad Sapkota",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": ""
        }    
                   
         ]
    }